bestappleprice.com 2016-06-25

# Welcome to the BestApplePrice.com Privacy Policy - BestApplePrice.com

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to help you understand what data we (as BestApplePrice.com) collect from you as a user, the reason behind it and how it is used. It is important that you take time to go through it thoroughly.

## Privacy Policy

Below privacy policy is applicable to all the users/visitors of BestApplePrice.com regardless of how, when and from where the sites is accessed. For details about terms of use, [click here](http://www.bestappleprice.com/terms-of-use).

### Personal & Non-Personal Information:

BestApplePrice.com does not collect any personal information about you as a user of this site (except in 2 cases – mentioned below). However, we and some of the 3rd party application that we use now (Google Analytics, Zopim, affiliate partners) or may use in future (Google AdSense) may use cookies to collect some non-personal information such as browser type, operating system, device type, internet service provider, your location, amount of time spent on site, sites you visited before visiting this site so on.

We consider this information as non-personal as they cannot be used to personally identify you. Such non-personal information is used by BestApplePrice.com to administer the website and perform various analysis to optimize the site’s content and performance.

This data could also be used by 3rd parties (including Google) to serve ads based on your prior visits to this and other websites. Click [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) for Google Ads privacy policy.

### Personal Information collected while availing Offline Chat Support or Leaving a Comment:

  * We do collect your name, email-id and phone number if you are availing offline chat support. The sole intent of collecting personal information on this front is to be able to contact you to address your concern (which is solely at the discretion of BestApplePrice.com).

  * While leaving a comment/feedback anywhere on the site using the comment form (found at the end of most of the pages on BestApplePrice.com), we ask you for your name and email address. The intent here again is to be able to reach you with respect to the comment you leave.

### Cookies

In order to analyse and optimize your usage experience based on how you interact with the site, BestApplePrice.com and 3rd parties may make use of cookies. You can disable the usage of cookies altogether by changing the appropriate browser settings.

### Affiliate Partners

BestApplePrice.com may redirect you to external 3rd party sites in which case the privacy policy of the appropriate site will govern. Since BestApplePrice.com has no control over the data collected by these 3rd parties (if any) it is advised to view their privacy policy. Any query/concern on the privacy policies of 3rd party/affiliate partners shall be directly taken with them.

### Privacy Policy Changes

BestApplePrice.com will, from time to time, update this privacy policy as it seems fit with clearly highlighting what has changed by updating this page with those changes. If you have any further questions or clarifications, feel free to contact us at info@bestappleprice.com or leave a comment and we will get in touch with you.

### Consent

Continuing to access BestApplePrice.com would mean that you confirm that you have read this privacy policy (in full) and give your consent to BestApplePrice.com and the 3rd parties (whose services BestApplePrice.com uses) to collect data, process and use it in accordance with this privacy policy.
